<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://www.tiktok.com/@alvine_n</id>
  <title>@alvine_n | TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-08T18:37:57+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="https://www.tiktok.com/@alvine_n" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://kickerofelves.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/alvine_n.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://kickerofelves.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>Latest TikToks from @alvine_n</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tiktok.com/@alvine_n/video/7264212731396508961</id>
    <title>Replying to @shamelesswrld3 Of course! Burning belly fat involves a combination of diet, cardiovascular exercise, and strength training. Here's a basic guide for beginners to start losing that belly fat: 1. Diet: Balanced Diet: Eat a balanced diet with le</title>
    <updated>2023-08-06T14:15:35+00:00</updated>
    <content>Replying to @shamelesswrld3 Of course! Burning belly fat involves a combination of diet, cardiovascular exercise, and strength training. Here's a basic guide for beginners to start losing that belly fat: 1. Diet: Balanced Diet: Eat a balanced diet with lean proteins, whole grains, healthy fats, and plenty of fruits and vegetables. Stay Hydrated: Drink at least 8 glasses of water daily. Avoid Sugar and Processed Foods: They can lead to weight gain and fat accumulation. Portion Control: Be aware of portion sizes and avoid overeating. 2. CardioExercise: Start Slow: If you're new to cardio, start with 15-20 minutes of moderate activity, like brisk walking. Gradually Increase: Increase the duration and intensity over time. Aim for at least 150 minutes per week. Variety: Mix up your routine. Walk, jog, cycle, or try aerobic classes. 3. Strength Training: Focus on Compound Movements: Exercises like squats, lunges, push-ups, and planks engage multiple muscle groups and help boost metabolism. Frequency: Aim for 2-3 times a week. Repetitions and Sets: As a beginner, start with 2 sets of 10-12 reps for each exercise, gradually increasing as you gain strength. 4. Core Exercises: Planks: Start with 20-30 seconds and build up to a minute or more. Russian Twists: Sit with your legs bent, lean back slightly, and twist side to side with or without a weight. Bicycle Crunches: Lie on your back, bring your knees to your chest, and alternate touching your opposite elbow to knee. 5. Stay Consistent: Routine: Stick to your workout and diet regimen. Consistency is key. Rest and Recovery: Ensure you get enough rest after workouts. Your muscles grow and repair during this time. #bellyfatburn #workoutbeginners</content>
    <link href="https://www.tiktok.com/@alvine_n/video/7264212731396508961" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-06T14:15:35+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tiktok.com/@alvine_n/video/7264655201422871840</id>
    <title>Gorilla row &gt;&gt; truth about gorilla row ; while the gorilla row is an excellent exercise for back development, achieving a "snatched" waist involves a combination of overall body fat reduction, targeted core training, and possibly genetic factors. You need</title>
    <updated>2023-08-07T18:52:31+00:00</updated>
    <content>Gorilla row &gt;&gt; truth about gorilla row ; while the gorilla row is an excellent exercise for back development, achieving a "snatched" waist involves a combination of overall body fat reduction, targeted core training, and possibly genetic factors. You need help? Join my body recomposition challenge in bio ❤️❤️❤️#gorillarowsworkout #backfat #snatched </content>
    <link href="https://www.tiktok.com/@alvine_n/video/7264655201422871840" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-07T18:52:31+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tiktok.com/@alvine_n/video/7264664001928269089</id>
    <title>Replying to @🦋 💎 strength training +diet 🔑</title>
    <updated>2023-08-07T19:26:40+00:00</updated>
    <content>Replying to @🦋 💎 strength training +diet 🔑</content>
    <link href="https://www.tiktok.com/@alvine_n/video/7264664001928269089" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-07T19:26:40+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tiktok.com/@alvine_n/video/7265014677631978785</id>
    <title>Replying to @aksk2012 Realistic day of eating; lose body fat &amp; gains 🍑⏳💪 more recipes on my cookbook </title>
    <updated>2023-08-08T18:07:28+00:00</updated>
    <content>Replying to @aksk2012 Realistic day of eating; lose body fat &amp; gains 🍑⏳💪 more recipes on my cookbook </content>
    <link href="https://www.tiktok.com/@alvine_n/video/7265014677631978785" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-08T18:07:28+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tiktok.com/@alvine_n/video/7265022526596730144</id>
    <title>@AYBL summer sale end tomorrow up to 60% off run code ALVINE ❤️ Use only 3 cable moves to build an hourglass figure and create the illusion of a smaller waist ⏳#HourglassFigure #FitnessJourney #CableWorkouts #workoutmotivation </title>
    <updated>2023-08-08T18:37:57+00:00</updated>
    <content>@AYBL summer sale end tomorrow up to 60% off run code ALVINE ❤️ Use only 3 cable moves to build an hourglass figure and create the illusion of a smaller waist ⏳#HourglassFigure #FitnessJourney #CableWorkouts #workoutmotivation </content>
    <link href="https://www.tiktok.com/@alvine_n/video/7265022526596730144" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-08T18:37:57+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
