<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://www.tiktok.com/@alvine_n</id>
  <title>@alvine_n | TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-07-17T19:18:22+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="https://www.tiktok.com/@alvine_n" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://kickerofelves.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/alvine_n.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://kickerofelves.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>Latest TikToks from @alvine_n</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tiktok.com/@alvine_n/video/7256385658350996763</id>
    <title>Replying to @a.arcxt   Glutes workout beginner friendly gym fit @AYBL  #gymmotivation </title>
    <updated>2023-07-16T12:02:31+00:00</updated>
    <content>Replying to @a.arcxt   Glutes workout beginner friendly gym fit @AYBL  #gymmotivation </content>
    <link href="https://www.tiktok.com/@alvine_n/video/7256385658350996763" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-16T12:02:31+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tiktok.com/@alvine_n/video/7256468932737912091</id>
    <title>Replying to @yo_girl_angie007   Workout plan + Nuttrition + private community chat for daily support &amp; motivation in bio ❤️</title>
    <updated>2023-07-16T17:25:39+00:00</updated>
    <content>Replying to @yo_girl_angie007   Workout plan + Nuttrition + private community chat for daily support &amp; motivation in bio ❤️</content>
    <link href="https://www.tiktok.com/@alvine_n/video/7256468932737912091" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-16T17:25:39+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tiktok.com/@alvine_n/video/7256805884565802267</id>
    <title>#CapCut ❤️Back &amp; Biceps for a Smaller Waist! 💪✨ Ready to sculpt those muscles and create a stunning waistline illusion? Check out this killer back and biceps workout video featuring some awesome exercises. 🔥 1️⃣ Kneeling Cable Lat Pull-Down with Rope: Eng</title>
    <updated>2023-07-17T15:13:12+00:00</updated>
    <content>#CapCut ❤️Back &amp; Biceps for a Smaller Waist! 💪✨ Ready to sculpt those muscles and create a stunning waistline illusion? Check out this killer back and biceps workout video featuring some awesome exercises. 🔥 1️⃣ Kneeling Cable Lat Pull-Down with Rope: Engage those lats and strengthen your back.3x15 2️⃣ Single Arm Dumbbell Row: Target each side individually for balanced development.4x8-12 each hand  3️⃣ Dumbbell Chest Supported Row: Focus on your upper back muscles with proper support. 4x8-12 4️⃣ Barbell Bicep Curls: Pump up those biceps for impressive arm definition. 4X8-12 5️⃣ Incline Dumbbell Reverse Flys: Sculpt your rear delts and improve posture. 3x15  6️⃣ Dumbbell Lateral Raises: Develop strong and shapely shoulders.3x15 7️⃣ Lat Pull-Down: Finish strong and give your back one final burn!4x8-12 #gymmotivation #backworkout </content>
    <link href="https://www.tiktok.com/@alvine_n/video/7256805884565802267" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-17T15:13:12+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tiktok.com/@alvine_n/video/7256854460641611034</id>
    <title>Replying to @beaulahLadimar   Hey TikTok fam! Are you ready to transform your waistline and achieve a flat tummy? Today, I'm sharing my proven 90-day challenge that has helped countless girlies achieve amazing results. Get ready to be inspired and motivat</title>
    <updated>2023-07-17T18:21:41+00:00</updated>
    <content>Replying to @beaulahLadimar   Hey TikTok fam! Are you ready to transform your waistline and achieve a flat tummy? Today, I'm sharing my proven 90-day challenge that has helped countless girlies achieve amazing results. Get ready to be inspired and motivated! Let's dive in! Set Clear Goals: "Before starting any transformation journey, it's essential to set clear and realistic goals. Write down how many inches you want to lose from your waist and the timeline you aim to achieve it in." Clean and Balanced Diet: "Achieving a snatched waist and flat tummy requires a healthy and balanced diet. Focus on nutrient-dense foods, such as lean proteins, fruits, vegetables, whole grains, and healthy fats. Avoid processed foods, sugary drinks, and excessive salt intake." Portion Control: "Maintain portion control to keep your calorie intake in check. Use smaller plates and bowls to trick your mind into feeling satisfied with smaller servings. Remember, it's not about depriving yourself but rather making mindful choices." Consistent Exercise Routine: "Combine cardio and strength training exercises to target your waistline and overall body fat. Incorporate exercises like planks, Russian twists, bicycle crunches, and side bends to specifically target your core. Aim for at least 30 minutes of exercise, five days a week." High-Intensity Interval Training (HIIT): "Include HIIT workouts in your routine to maximize fat burning and boost metabolism. HIIT involves short bursts of intense exercises followed by brief recovery periods. This helps burn calories even after your workout." Stay Hydrated: "Drink plenty of water throughout the day to stay hydrated and support your body's metabolism. Replace sugary drinks with water or herbal teas to avoid unnecessary calories." Get Enough Sleep: "Adequate sleep is crucial for weight loss and overall well-being. Aim for 7-9 hours of quality sleep each night. Lack of sleep can lead to increased hunger hormones, affecting your waistline goals." Stay Consistent and Motivated: "Remember, transforming your waistline and achieving a flat tummy takes time and effort. Stay consistent with your diet and exercise routine, even on days when motivation is low. Find inspiration from success stories and celebrate every milestone. So there you have it! Follow these tips and join our 90-day challenge to achieve a snatched waist and flat tummy. Don't forget to check out the incredible transformation pictures from our bestie who have lost up to 33lbs in just 6 weeks! Let's crush our goals together! Like and share this video to spread the inspiration. See you in the next update! 💪🔥</content>
    <link href="https://www.tiktok.com/@alvine_n/video/7256854460641611034" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-17T18:21:41+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tiktok.com/@alvine_n/video/7256869067708042523</id>
    <title>Replying to @sanchezeronsma   Wake up😅</title>
    <updated>2023-07-17T19:18:22+00:00</updated>
    <content>Replying to @sanchezeronsma   Wake up😅</content>
    <link href="https://www.tiktok.com/@alvine_n/video/7256869067708042523" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-17T19:18:22+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
