<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://www.tiktok.com/@korpobrownskin</id>
  <title>@korpobrownskin | TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-07-27T14:44:01+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="https://www.tiktok.com/@korpobrownskin" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://kickerofelves.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/korpobrownskin.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://kickerofelves.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>Latest TikToks from @korpobrownskin</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tiktok.com/@korpobrownskin/video/7257504162689338630</id>
    <title>Replying to @The Rookie first link in my bio to sign up for my “ 60 day snatch that body challenge” structured meal plan and private community. #howtogetridoffupa #lovehandlesworkout #fitnessmotivation #foryoupage </title>
    <updated>2023-07-19T12:22:48+00:00</updated>
    <content>Replying to @The Rookie first link in my bio to sign up for my “ 60 day snatch that body challenge” structured meal plan and private community. #howtogetridoffupa #lovehandlesworkout #fitnessmotivation #foryoupage </content>
    <link href="https://www.tiktok.com/@korpobrownskin/video/7257504162689338630" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-19T12:22:48+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tiktok.com/@korpobrownskin/video/7259410602882305286</id>
    <title>6 months left Besties We’re Fierce and Fearless, Sis! Crush Those Goals! 🎯 No goal is too big for us! My 60-day challenge has everything we need to slay. Let’s conquer the world, one workout at a time! Link in bio. #FearlessFitnessSquad #SlayTogether #Cru</title>
    <updated>2023-07-24T15:40:46+00:00</updated>
    <content>6 months left Besties We’re Fierce and Fearless, Sis! Crush Those Goals! 🎯 No goal is too big for us! My 60-day challenge has everything we need to slay. Let’s conquer the world, one workout at a time! Link in bio. #FearlessFitnessSquad #SlayTogether #CrushYourGoals #foryoupage #fitnessmotivation </content>
    <link href="https://www.tiktok.com/@korpobrownskin/video/7259410602882305286" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-24T15:40:46+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tiktok.com/@korpobrownskin/video/7259770800700509446</id>
    <title>Replying to @ebony ᥫ᭡ tone your back and snatch your waist ⌛️ Besties, 2024 is only 5 months away. You started this year with goals how close are you now? Are you happy happy or feeling confident with your present body ? No judgment over here judt these a</title>
    <updated>2023-07-25T14:58:31+00:00</updated>
    <content>Replying to @ebony ᥫ᭡ tone your back and snatch your waist ⌛️ Besties, 2024 is only 5 months away. You started this year with goals how close are you now? Are you happy happy or feeling confident with your present body ? No judgment over here judt these are questions and reminder to not give up, keep pushing. Link is in my bio to start your journey and kill the remaining months, structured meal plan and private community for support  #backday #backexercises #fyp</content>
    <link href="https://www.tiktok.com/@korpobrownskin/video/7259770800700509446" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-25T14:58:31+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tiktok.com/@korpobrownskin/video/7260135627977411846</id>
    <title>your goal right now is to grow thicc rounded Bunda and you're less than 1200 calories per day then of course you're not going to see encouraging results If you're goal right now is to lose weight but also want to grow your glutes while in the process then</title>
    <updated>2023-07-26T14:34:13+00:00</updated>
    <content>your goal right now is to grow thicc rounded Bunda and you're less than 1200 calories per day then of course you're not going to see encouraging results If you're goal right now is to lose weight but also want to grow your glutes while in the process then there is nothing wrong with eating in calories deficit because that's how you'll achieve your weight loss( and if you approach what you eat daily then you can literally RECOMPOSITION your entire body while loosing weight ) Most times we apply all the right gym methods but forgetting nutrition play a huge part to our fitness journey, if you're eating as low 1200 or less calories per day for whatever your goals are and expecting to make progress that is also nearly impossible because your body need fuel and food is the fuel, reasons why i tell my Besties to have balance diet. You need fuel to have you lift heavy and push through your cardio. Eat well and turn those food into good gains by being active. I know it's hard hearing you need to eat in order to see progress, I used to be one of those people who think eating very little food will make me not fat, lose weight or gain weight so I totally get it. Most times you also don't even know what to eat or how much calories you're even taking per day , it's time to stop fearing food especially if you haven't seen much progress in your journey. Listen, If you haven't been seeing progress in the gym If you've been lacking motivation to train If you're wondering why you're not building any muscle If you've been worn out, tired or lethargic If you're frustrated with feeling overwhelmed or burnt out Join my team first link ⬆️🔗 in my bio to sign up for my 60 day program and custom meal plan. I can guarantee result in 60 day #6exercisestogrowyourglutes #glutegrowth #legdayworkout #howtogrowGLUTES #fitnesstips </content>
    <link href="https://www.tiktok.com/@korpobrownskin/video/7260135627977411846" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-26T14:34:13+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tiktok.com/@korpobrownskin/video/7260509209379343621</id>
    <title>Alcohol slows your metabolism down when creating your dream body! There are sacrifices you have to make if you're on your weight loss journey and that highly include sugary beverages or food consumption especially ALCOHOL  Let the Happy Hour and lay loose</title>
    <updated>2023-07-27T14:44:01+00:00</updated>
    <content>Alcohol slows your metabolism down when creating your dream body! There are sacrifices you have to make if you're on your weight loss journey and that highly include sugary beverages or food consumption especially ALCOHOL  Let the Happy Hour and lay loose weekend it alcohol go not saying forever but whilst on this journey give your body the grace to achieve the result from the work you put in. Basic drink like alcohol have to go until you're close to your goal. Give yourself the next 60 days to be properly sober eat well, be active and I guarantee you'll see more achievements than ever Join my team ⬆️! first link 🔗🔗in my bio to sign up for my 60 day snatch that body challenge. Let's fight this @Legion Athletics together besties Pre-workout and surge performance “ bad combo 🔥” use code: KORPO 15%  #functionalcoreworkout #compoundmovements #howtogrowglutesandlosebellyfat #legsandglutes #howtotoneback #howtotonearms </content>
    <link href="https://www.tiktok.com/@korpobrownskin/video/7260509209379343621" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-07-27T14:44:01+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
