<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://www.tiktok.com/@korpobrownskin</id>
  <title>@korpobrownskin | TikTok</title>
  <updated>2023-08-16T16:53:36+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Conor ONeill</name>
    <email>conor@conoroneill.com</email>
  </author>
  <link href="https://www.tiktok.com/@korpobrownskin" rel="alternate"/>
  <link href="https://kickerofelves.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/rss/korpobrownskin.xml" rel="self"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="0.9.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <logo>https://kickerofelves.github.io/tiktok-rss-flat/tiktok-rss.png</logo>
  <subtitle>Latest TikToks from @korpobrownskin</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tiktok.com/@korpobrownskin/video/7265808742212521222</id>
    <title>The cheat code to building your hourglass figure is training upper body 1/2 times as you train legs. Training back give you the illusion of hourglass figure  ✅ wide gripe lat pull down ✅ lat pull down  Join my community ⬆️⬆️🔗🔗 first link in my bio . Home </title>
    <updated>2023-08-10T21:28:48+00:00</updated>
    <content>The cheat code to building your hourglass figure is training upper body 1/2 times as you train legs. Training back give you the illusion of hourglass figure  ✅ wide gripe lat pull down ✅ lat pull down  Join my community ⬆️⬆️🔗🔗 first link in my bio . Home and edition, structured meal plan , private community. Pre workout &amp; performance surge  “ code KORPO for 15% off”  #latpulldown #backworkout #howtotoneback #howtomovebackfat #backday </content>
    <link href="https://www.tiktok.com/@korpobrownskin/video/7265808742212521222" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-10T21:28:48+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tiktok.com/@korpobrownskin/video/7266491051655941382</id>
    <title>#fyp #viral #fouryoupage </title>
    <updated>2023-08-12T17:36:32+00:00</updated>
    <content>#fyp #viral #fouryoupage </content>
    <link href="https://www.tiktok.com/@korpobrownskin/video/7266491051655941382" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-12T17:36:32+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tiktok.com/@korpobrownskin/video/7266521771774446854</id>
    <title>Besties , 2024 is 5months away. This is the reminder you needed to see today, you started this year with a goal how far are you now?  You said this year was going to be the year you achieve your dream body , it’s hard and life can be full of ups and downs</title>
    <updated>2023-08-12T19:35:44+00:00</updated>
    <content>Besties , 2024 is 5months away. This is the reminder you needed to see today, you started this year with a goal how far are you now?  You said this year was going to be the year you achieve your dream body , it’s hard and life can be full of ups and downs but dont forget to give yourself grace to take care of you .  🚨Join my community where like minded women are encouraging each other to push through. First link🔗 in my bio ⬆️⬆️ home and gym workout , custom meal plan and private community for daily motivation. Besties you’re not alone on this journey  #fitnessmotivation #fitnesstips #fyp #backday </content>
    <link href="https://www.tiktok.com/@korpobrownskin/video/7266521771774446854" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-12T19:35:44+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tiktok.com/@korpobrownskin/video/7267340060159151366</id>
    <title>If you're performing hip abductor and you don't feel that burning sensation just in 5 reps, try the third slide! Place your hands at the edge of the seat. The burn in your glute medius will make your eyes wet from hot tears 5 reps slow, 5 reps fast, 5 rep</title>
    <updated>2023-08-15T00:31:08+00:00</updated>
    <content>If you're performing hip abductor and you don't feel that burning sensation just in 5 reps, try the third slide! Place your hands at the edge of the seat. The burn in your glute medius will make your eyes wet from hot tears 5 reps slow, 5 reps fast, 5 reps slow pause If you haven't sign up for my "60 day Snatch that body "first link 🔗⬆️in my bio. Home and gym workout plan, structured meal plan and private community. Join my team #hipabductionmachine #hipabductor #glutesmedius #howtogrowupperglutes #howtofixhipdips #glutesworkout #glutegrowth #foryoupage </content>
    <link href="https://www.tiktok.com/@korpobrownskin/video/7267340060159151366" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-15T00:31:08+00:00</published>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.tiktok.com/@korpobrownskin/video/7267964330266692870</id>
    <title>1. Eat lean protein: you want to make sure you go for the leaner cuts of those meats like chicken breast maybe the thighs but leave the drum sticks alone. If you're having ground beef make sure to ask for 5-6% fat ONLY. 2. Try to eat set time: instead of </title>
    <updated>2023-08-16T16:53:36+00:00</updated>
    <content>1. Eat lean protein: you want to make sure you go for the leaner cuts of those meats like chicken breast maybe the thighs but leave the drum sticks alone. If you're having ground beef make sure to ask for 5-6% fat ONLY. 2. Try to eat set time: instead of combining your whole day food and eating it at once at the end of the day why not separate your meals at least it help you know how much you're consuming. Breakfast, lunch and dinner. If you're doing your 9-5 and no time to come back home to make your lunch why not make yourself a lunch box! When creating your dream body you need to make some sacrifices! 3. Try to meal prep on Sunday or whatever day good for you: make sure you're not doing takeout regularly. Stop buying processed food and try to cook home this will help you control the amount of calories especially coming from your oil and seasoning. Most of those foods prepared outside are high in calories and low on proteins 4. Alcohol and sugary beverages: alcohol on the regular is bad for your system less to talk about how it slows down your metabolism. It's true almost all of our foods possess lab sugar but also topping it up with pure full sugar food won't help you lose that stubborn tummy, bat wing /arm fat , or back fat. Let go of these for now 5. have good sleep: in as much this may sound simple it really be the cause you're not dropping off that dead weight. If you don't get enough rest, you're tired and when you're tired you're More likely to eat more. Tiredness actually increases a chemical in your system called ghrelin and that upregulates which mean you're more hungry when you're tired. Try to manage your stress level so you can have a sound deep sleep Join my community ⬆️⬆️  first link in my bio 🔗🔗 structure meal plan  #lamdmineworkout #landminelegandglute #legday #singlelegrdl #glutegrowth ##landminesquat #foryoupage #viral #caloriedeficittoloseweight </content>
    <link href="https://www.tiktok.com/@korpobrownskin/video/7267964330266692870" rel="alternate"/>
    <published>2023-08-16T16:53:36+00:00</published>
  </entry>
</feed>
